Guide to the Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1965-2012; Series VI; 13.3; (24 boxes)
  - 8x10 Photographs, 1965-2012
    - Dave Eggers, undated (Box 63)
    - Amanda Eicher installation Adobe Books, February 2007, 2007 February (Box 63)
    - Jacob Eichert, undated (Box 63)
    - Kate Eichorn, undated (Box 63)
    - Hedi El-Khouti, undated (Box 63)
    - Lewis Ellingham, 76th birthday, undated (Box 63)
    - Stephen Elliott, undated (Box 74)
    - Kenward Elmslie, undated (Box 63)
    - Laura Elrick and Jocelyn Saidenberg, undated (Box 63)
    - Hassan El Sherbiny, undated (Box 63)
    - David Enos, undated (Box 63)
    - Theodore Enslin, undated (Box 63)
    - Andrew Epstein, undated (Box 63)
    - Elaine Equi aml Kevin Killian, undated (Box 63)
    - Elaine Equi and Jerome Sala, undated (Box 63)
    - Kevin embracing the tomb of Erasmus, undated (Box 63)
    - Alicia Escott, undated (Box 63)
    - Logan Esdale, undated (Box 63)
    - Patricia Esquivias, undated (Box 63)
    - Essay Class Spring 2006, 2006 Spring (Box 63)
    - Jordan Essoe in "The Propeller", undated (Box 63)
    - Valerie Estes, undated (Box 63)
    - Ethel Chase memorial, undated (Box 63)
    - Eva and Adele, Art Basel 38, undated (Box 63)
    - Amy Evans, undated (Box 63)
    - Simon Evans, undated (Box 63)
    - Steve Evans, undated (Box 74)
    - Thomas Evans, undated (Box 63)
    - Brian Evenson, undated (Box 63)
    - Liam Everett, undated (Box 63)
    - Landis Everson, undated (Box 63)
    - Landis Everson's painting "Marguerites", undated (Box 63)
    - Mark Ewert, undated (Box 63)
    - Marcus Ewert as "Dobby the Elf" Slaying Mark Ewert, with wand, after Harry Potter, undated (Box 63)
    - Anna Eyre, undated (Box 63)
    - Kota Ezawa, undated (Box 63)
    - Kota Ezawa exhibition at Wattis Institute, summer 2006, 2006 Summer (Box 63)
    - Kota Ezawa directing Kevin Killian, undated (Box 63)
    - Zora Ezawa on Thomas Hirschhorn's camouflage sofa, undated (Box 63)
    - Gerald Fabian, undated (Box 63)
    - Adam Fagin, undated (Box 63)
    - Falling exhibition at Right Window, August 2008, 2008 August (Box 63)
    - Ben Fama, undated (Box 63)
    - Steven Fama, undated (Box 63)
    - Geoffrey Farmer, undated (Box 63)
    - Steven Farmer, undated (Box 63)
    - Dan Farrell, undated (Box 63)
    - Michael Farrell, undated (Box 63)
    - Denise Farrington, undated (Box 63)
    - Lisa and Leslie Farrington, undated (Box 63)
    - Leslie Farrington and Ivory Griggs, undated (Box 63)
    - David Farwell, undated (Box 63)
    - Monica Fauble, undated (Box 63)
    - Bruno Fazzolari, undated (Box 63)
    - Vincent Fecteau, undated (Box 63)
    - Vincent Fecteau, open studio, July 2008, 2008 July (Box 63)
    - Raymond Federmart, undated (Box 63)
    - Federman's toes, undated (Box 63)
    - Rachel Feinstein, undated (Box 63)
    - Melissa K. Feldman, undated (Box 63)
    - Andrew Felsinger, undated (Box 63)
    - Chris Felver, undated (Box 63)
    - Lawrence Ferlinghetti, undated (Box 63)
    - Les Ferriss, undated (Box 63)
    - Amanda Field, undated (Box 63)
    - Johnny Fierer, Boulder friend of Chris and Brian, undated (Box 63)
    - 1559 Pacific Avenue, San Francisco apartment of Elizabeth Bishop, undated (Box 63)
    - Dan Fine, undated (Box 63)
    - Jennifer Natalya Fink, undated (Box 63)
    - Thomas Fink, undated (Box 63)
    - Fireworks at Beany Convention in Portland, undated (Box 63)
    - Julia Fish, undated (Box 63)
    - Matt Fishbeck, undated (Box 63)
    - Andy Fitch, undated (Box 63)
    - Rob Fitterman, undated (Box 63)
    - Chris Fitzpatrick and Kota Ezawa, undated (Box 63)
    - Michael Flanagan, undated (Box 63)
    - Matt Flegle with a boot up his ass, undated (Box 63)
    - Matt Flegle as Disco Frankenstein, undated (Box 63)
    - Henry Flesh, undated (Box 63)
    - Paul Stojsavljecvic Flores, undated (Box 63)
    - Sandy Florian, undated (Box 63)
    - Robert Flynt, undated (Box 63)
    - Katherine V. Forrest, undated (Box 63)
    - Sesshu Foster, undated (Box 63)
    - Tonya Foster, undated (Box 63)
    - Graham Foust, undated (Box 63)
    - Kate Fowle, undated (Box 63)
    - Kate Fowle and Matthew Post, undated (Box 63)
    - Brendan Fowler, undated (Box 63)
    - Thad Fowler, undated (Box 63)
    - Marc Foxx, undated (Box 64)
    - Amy Franceschini, undated (Box 64)
    - Kathleen Fraser, undated (Box 64)
    - Stephen Fredman, undated (Box 64)
    - David Friedman, undated (Box 64)
    - Michael Friedman, undated (Box 64)
    - Peach Friedman, undated (Box 64)
    - Jack Fritscher, undated (Box 64)
    - Chris Frizzelle, undated (Box 64)
    - Aurelien Froment, undated (Box 64)
    - Richard Froude, undated (Box 64)
    - Simon Fujiwara, undated (Box 64)
    - Ryan Funk, undated (Box 64)
    - Maxine Gadd, undated (Box 64)
    - Cyprien Gaillard, undated (Box 64)
    - Mary Gaitskill, undated (Box 64)
    - Kristen Gallagher, undated (Box 64)
    - Gallery Central Park (fictitious novel), undated (Box 64)
    - Arturo Galster, undated (Box 64)
    - Forrest Gander, undated (Box 64)
    - Ryan Gander, undated (Box 64)
    - Herair Garboushian, undated (Box 64)
    - Dora Garcia, undated (Box 64)
    - Mario Garcia Torres, undated (Box 64)
    - Drew Gardner and Katie Degentesh, undated (Box 64)
    - Susana Gardner, undated (Box 64)
    - Gary Garrels, undated (Box 64)
    - William Joseph Gass, "Study for Self Employment", undated (Box 64)
    - Charles Gatewood, undated (Box 64)
    - Geoffrey Gatza, undated (Box 64)
    - Linda Geary, undated (Box 64)
    - Frank Gehry bandshell at Millennium Park, Chicago, undated (Box 64)
    - Matthias Geiger, undated (Box 64)
    - Philip Gerard, undated (Box 64)
    - Rick Gerharter, undated (Box 64)
    - Giant Camera, undated (Box 64)
    - Alan Gilbert, undated (Box 64)
    - Ed Gilbert, undated (Box 64)
    - Geoff Gilbert, undated (Box 64)
    - Alex Gildzen's tie around Kevin's neck and cock, undated (Box 64)
    - Samantha Giles, undated (Box 64)
    - Merrill Gilfallan, undated (Box 64)
    - Bryson Gill, undated (Box 64)
    - Larry Gilmore, undated (Box 64)
    - Jon Ginoli, undated (Box 64)
    - Lara Glenum, undated (Box 64)
    - Madeline Gins, undated (Box 64)
    - John Giorno, undated (Box 64)
    - Photios G iovanis, undated (Box 64)
    - Chris Girard, undated (Box 64)
    - Girls of the KSW (Guinevere Pencarrick, Andrea Actis, Dorothy Trujillo Lusk), undated (Box 64)
    - C.S. Giscombe, undated (Box 64)
    - Peter Gizzi and Kevin Killian, photo by Dodie Bellamy, undated (Box 64)
    - Renee Gladman, undated (Box 64)
    - Diane Glancy, undated (Box 64)
    - Lara Glenum, undated (Box 64)
    - Chris Glomski, undated (Box 64)
    - Robert Gluck, undated (Box 64)
    - Robert Gluck and Robin Blaser, undated (Box 64)
    - Robert Gluck and Kevin Killian, undated (Box 64)
    - Mark Gluth, undated (Box 64)
    - Mark Gluth and Erin Kelly, undated (Box 64)
    - James Gobel with heroic self-portrait in men's room, SF Eagle, undated (Box 64)
    - John Godfrey, undated (Box 74)
    - Laurie Gold and Sarah Schulman, undated (Box 64)
    - Gravity Goldberg, undated (Box 64)
    - Alan Golding, undated (Box 64)
    - Kenneth Goldsmith, undated (Box 64)
    - Emily Gonzalez, undated (Box 64)
    - Matt Gonzalez, undated (Box 64)
    - Veronica Gonzalez, undated (Box 64)
    - Philip Good, undated (Box 64)
    - Craig Goodman, undated (Box 64)
    - Goodwill Attendant in Pink Clown Wig, undated (Box 64)
    - Johannes Goranson, undated (Box 64)
    - Matthew Gordon, undated (Box 64)
    - Matthew Gordon and Chris Fitzpatrick, undated (Box 64)
    - Matthew Gordon and Matthew Gordan, undated (Box 64)
    - Noah Eli Gordon, undated (Box 64)
    - Sam Gordon, undated (Box 64)
    - Les Gottesman, undated (Box 64)
    - Daphne Gottlieb, undated (Box 64)
    - Michael Gottlieb, undated (Box 64)
    - Sam Gould/Red 76, undated (Box 64)
    - Dan Gower of Ching Chong Song, undated (Box 64)
    - Jay Grabowski, undated (Box 64)
    - Graffiti, undated (Box 64)
    - K. Lorraine Graham, undated (Box 64)
    - Paul Graham, undated (Box 64)
    - Judy Grahn, undated (Box 64)
    - John Granger, undated (Box 64)
    - Timothy Gray, undated (Box 64)
    - Jeremy Green, undated (Box 64)
    - (Green shoes), undated (Box 64)
    - Matthew Greene and Trinie Dalton, undated (Box 64)
    - Kate Greenstreet, undated (Box 64)
    - Ted Greenwald, undated (Box 64)
    - James Greer, undated (Box 64)
    - Andrew Sean Greer, undated (Box 64)
    - Brenden Gregory, undated (Box 64)
    - Andy Gricevich, undated (Box 64)
    - Susan Griffin, undated (Box 64)
    - Rosemary Griggs, undated (Box 64)
    - Tim Griffin, undated (Box 64)
    - Tracy Grinnell, undated (Box 64)
    - Mark Grotjahn, undated (Box 64)
    - Barbara Guest, undated (Box 64)
    - Graham Guest, undated (Box 64)
    - Michael Guidetti in front of Brett, undated (Box 64)
    - Reichman picture, undated (Box 64)
    - Christian Gullette, undated (Box 64)
    - Christian Gullette and Brent Calderwood, undated (Box 64)
    - Thom Gunn, undated (Box 64)
    - Myriam Gurba, undated (Box 64)
    - The Gurlesque: Lara Glenum and Joyelle Mcsweeney, undated (Box 64)
    - Annie Guthrie, undated (Box 64)
    - Janice Guy, undated (Box 64)
    - Leonie Guyer, undated (Box 64)
    - Pierre Guyotat, undated (Box 64)
    - Pierre Guyotat and Hedi El-Khouti, undated (Box 64)
    - Brion Gysin spirit photo, undated (Box 64)
    - Zack Haber, undated (Box 65)
    - David Hadbawnik, undated (Box 65)
    - Bruce Hainley, undated (Box 65)
    - Liz Halafia taking my picture, undated (Box 65)
    - Jeremy Halinen, undated (Box 65)
    - Thomas Ray Hall, undated (Box 65)
    - Greg Halpern, undated (Box 65)
    - Rob Halpern, undated (Box 65)
    - Anne Hamersky, undated (Box 65)
    - Andrew Hamilton, undated (Box 65)
    - Jonathan Hammer, undated (Box 65)
    - Jason Hanasik, undated (Box 65)
    - Jason Hanasikand Billy Miller, undated (Box 65)
    - Q. R. Hand, undated (Box 65)
    - Jack Hanley, undated (Box 65)
    - Mr and Mrs. David Hannah, undated (Box 65)
    - Terence Hannum, undated (Box 65)
    - Kaplan Page Harris, undated (Box 65)
    - Dave Haselwood, undated (Box 65)
    - Skyler Haskard, undated (Box 65)
    - Skyler Haskard, Aida Ruilova, and Raymond Pettibon, undated (Box 65)
    - Elizabeth Hatmaker, undated (Box 65)
    - Patsy Hatt, undated (Box 65)
    - Johnnie Hattori, undated (Box 65)
    - Bobbie Louise Hawkins on her 80th birthday, undated (Box 65)
    - Jared Hayes, undated (Box 65)
    - Terrance Hayes, undated (Box 65)
    - Thai Sculpture, Hayes Park, undated (Box 65)
    - Trebor Healey, undated (Box 65)
    - Eloise Klein Healy, undated (Box 65)
    - Erin Heath, undated (Box 65)
    - Michael Layne Heath, undated (Box 65)
    - Scott Heim, undated (Box 65)
    - Heklina, founder of Trannyshack, undated (Box 65)
    - Glen Helfand, undated (Box 65)
    - Maxwell Heller, undated (Box 65)
    - Sophie von Hellerman, undated (Box 65)
    - Clifford Hengst, undated (Box 65)
    - Keith Hennessy, undated (Box 65)
    - Beth Henson, undated (Box 65)
    - Colin Herd, undated (Box 65)
    - Sofia Hernandez Chong Cuy, undated (Box 65)
    - Fran Herndon, undated (Box 65)
    - Fran Herndon and Scott Watson, undated (Box 65)
    - Fran Herndon and Kal Spelletich, undated (Box 65)
    - Fran Herndon and Rebecca Bollinger, undated (Box 65)
    - Tamara, Jack, and Fran Herndon, undated (Box 65)
    - Jonny Heron, undated (Box 65)
    - Oliver Herring, undated (Box 65)
    - Lynn Hershman Leeson, undated (Box 65)
    - David Hess, undated (Box 65)
    - Greg Hewett, undated (Box 65)
    - Scott Hewicker, undated (Box 65)
    - Scott Hewicker and Aaron Peck, undated (Box 65)
    - Tom Hewicker, undated (Box 65)
    - Sander Hicks and "White Collar Crime", undated (Box 65)
    - High Energy Constructs, undated (Box 65)
    - Mitch Highfill, undated (Box 65)
    - Highland Gardens Motel, undated (Box 65)
    - Lindsay Hill, undated (Box 65)
    - Rodney Hill at Ryan Gander show, Marc Foxx Gallery, undated (Box 65)
    - Brenda Hillman, undated (Box 65)
    - Thea Hillman, undated (Box 65)
    - Daniel Hipolito, undated (Box 65)
    - Thomas Hirschhorn, undated (Box 65)
    - Jack Hirschman, undated (Box 65)
    - William "Gatz" Hjortsberg, undated (Box 65)
    - Brice Hobbs, undated (Box 65)
    - Hobbypop Museum (Andre Niebur and Dietmar Lutz), undated (Box 74)
    - J. Haberman, undated (Box 65)
    - Kevin Hobson, undated (Box 65)
    - Ida Hodes, undated (Box 65)
    - Jen Hofer, undated (Box 65)
    - Jens Hoffmann, undated (Box 65)
    - Jens Hoffmann and Marc Foxx, undated (Box 65)
    - Reiner Hohndorf, energy theoretician, undated (Box 65)
    - Kristen Holden, undated (Box 65)
    - Carsten Holler, "Wonderful", undated (Box 65)
    - Nicole Hollis, undated (Box 65)
    - Tanya Hollis, undated (Box 65)
    - Tanya Hollis and Yedda Morrison, undated (Box 65)
    - Evan Holloway, undated (Box 65)
    - Brandon Drew Holmes, undated (Box 65)
    - Michael Hooper, undated (Box 65)
    - Phillip Hoover, undated (Box 65)
    - Gannett Hosa, undated (Box 65)
    - Yuri Hospodar, undated (Box 65)
    - Hotel where Steve and Jennifer stayed MLA, Chicago 2007 (Box 65)
    - Franscois Houle, undated (Box 65)
    - Joanna Howard, undated (Box 65)
    - Susan Howe, undated (Box 65)
    - Andrew Hoyem, undated (Box 65)
    - Sarah Hromack, undated (Box 65)
    - Bill Hsu, undated (Box 65)
    - Hudson, undated (Box 65)
    - David Hull, undated (Box 65)
    - Christine Hume, undated (Box 65)
    - Erica Hunt, undated (Box 65)
    - Hunt (detail) by D-L Alvarez in Kiki show, undated (Box 65)
    - Bo Huston, undated (Box 65)
    - Martin Hyatt, undated (Box 65)
    - John Hyland as Nurse Ratched, Buffalo 2009 (Box 65)
    - Hypnotic Show, spring 2008, 2008 Spring (Box 65)
    - Jess's painting Icarus, undated (Box 65)
    - Mark Ibold from Pavement, undated (Box 65)
    - Bethany Ides, undated (Box 65)
    - Illegitimate Business show, February 2012, 2012 February (Box 65)
    - Scott Inguito, undated (Box 65)
    - P. Inman, undated (Box 65)
    - Institute for Figuring Right Window installation, September 2008, 2008 September (Box 65)
    - Sam Irvin, undated (Box 65)
    - Irving and La Playa, undated (Box 65)
    - Livia Isaacson and Jason Morris, undated (Box 65)
    - Doug lschar, undated (Box 65)
    - Tara Ison, undated (Box 65)
    - Kathe Izzo, undated (Box 65)
    - Earl Jackson, Jr., undated (Box 65)
    - Jo Jackson, Donal Mosher, and Justine at Beautiful Losers opening YBCA, summer 2004, 2004 Summer (Box 65)
    - Shelley Jackson, undated (Box 65)
    - Colter Jacobsen, undated (Box 65)
    - Colter Jacobsen at Sunrise Laundromat lecturing, June 2006, 2006 June (Box 65)
    - Colter Jacobsen wearing Kathy Acker's jacket, undated (Box 65)
    - Colter Jacobsen and Scott Hewicker, undated (Box 65)
    - Colter Jacobsen as "Buttons" the clown, undated (Box 65)
    - Hands of Colter Jacobsen, undated (Box 65)
    - Colter's Moby Dick painting, undated (Box 65)
    - Colter Jacobsen and Elijah Burgher, undated (Box 65)
    - Jill Jacobsen and her son Will Campbell, undated (Box 65)
    - Rick (Jacobsen) by Keith Mayerson, undated (Box 66)
    - Rick Jacobsen, undated (Box 66)
    - Harry Jacobus on easel, undated (Box 66)
    - Mytili Jagannathan, undated (Box 66)
    - Jason Jagel, undated (Box 66)
    - Evan James and Matt Briggs, undated (Box 66)
    - Gina James, undated (Box 66)
    - Gina James' piano, decorated by Jess, undated (Box 66)
    - Marlon James, undated (Box 66)
    - Piotr Janas, undated (Box 66)
    - Xylor Jane, undated (Box 66)
    - Jani, undated (Box 66)
    - Lisa Jarnot, undated (Box 66)
    - Aaron Jason, undated (Box 66)
    - Paolo Javier, undated (Box 66)
    - Joan Jeanrenaud, undated (Box 66)
    - Adriene Jenik, undated (Box 66)
    - Philip Jenks, undated (Box 66)
    - Terri Jentz, undated (Box 66)
    - Travis Jeppesen, undated (Box 66)
    - Warner Jepson, undated (Box 66)
    - Jess by Fran Herndon, 1965 (Box 66)
    - Jetblue Legroom, undated (Box 66)
    - Jason Jimenez, undated (Box 66)
    - Chris Johanson, undated (Box 66)
    - Chris Johanson painting in collection of Jim Winters, undated (Box 66)
    - Reg Johanson, undated (Box 66)
    - David Johnson, undated (Box 74)
    - Fenton Johnson, undated (Box 66)
    - Kent Johnson, undated (Box 66)
    - Paul Foster Johnson, undated (Box 66)
    - David E. Johnstone, undated (Box 66)
    - Eric Renehan Jones, undated (Box 66)
    - Sarah Jones, undated (Box 74)
    - William E. Jones, undated (Box 66)
    - Tim Jones-Yelvington, undated (Box 66)
    - Room ro6, Highland Gardens Motel, where Janis Joplin died, undated (Box 66)
    - Lawrence Jordan, undated (Box 66)
    - Josh, the boyfriend of Darrell, undated (Box 66)
    - Gabriela Juaregui, undated (Box 66)
    - Isaac Julien, undated (Box 66)
    - Brian Jungen, undated (Box 66)
    - The Letter "K'', undated (Box 66)
    - Emilia and Ilya Kabakov, undated (Box 66)
    - Jason Kalogiros, undated (Box 66)
    - Jakub Kalousek, undated (Box 66)
    - Ilya Kaminsky, undated (Box 66)
    - Daniel Kane, undated (Box 66)
    - Bhanu Kapil, undated (Box 66)
    - Gregory Kaplowitz, undated (Box 66)
    - Anish Kapoor's "Bean" sculpture at Millennium Park, Chicago, undated (Box 66)
    - Anish Kapoor installation at Art Basel 38, undated (Box 66)
    - Adeena Karasick, undated (Box 66)
    - Kabin Karki, undated (Box 66)
    - Michael Karo, undated (Box 66)
    - Kathy Forest (Dodie Bellamy) exhibition at White Columns, January 2007, 2007 January (Box 66)
    - Justin Katko, undated (Box 66)
    - Daniel Katz, undated (Box 66)
    - Jonathan David Katz, undated (Box 66)
    - Erica Kaufman, undated (Box 66)
    - Lenny Kaye and Patti Smith, undated (Box 66)
    - Rachel Kaye, undated (Box 66)
    - Douglas Kearney, undated (Box 66)
    - Larry Kearney, undated (Box 66)
    - Matt Keegan, undated (Box 66)
    - Evan Kennedy, undated (Box 66)
    - Evan Kennedy, my photo of him, and his birthday cake, undated (Box 66)
    - Meaghan Kennedy of Vancouver's Haute Couture Pinatas (and her friend, Kyle), undated (Box 66)
    - Brian Kennon, undated (Box 66)
    - Niki Kerr (Tariq Alvi's designer friend), undated (Box 66)
    - Brad Kessler, undated (Box 66)
    - Jussi Ketonen and Rachel Loden, undated (Box 66)
    - Keynote Speakers (Orono 2008): Tom Raworth, Fred Wah, Bruce Andrews, Clark Coolidge, Ann Lauterbach (Box 66)
    - Aaron Kiely, undated (Box 66)
    - Kiki poster in Adobe Books window, undated (Box 66)
    - Kiki signage by Colter Jacobsen, undated (Box 66)
    - David Killian, undated (Box 66)
    - Howard Killian, undated (Box 66)
    - The two Kevin Killians, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian, photos by William E. Jones, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian, photo by Michael Guidetti, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Dario Argento, undated (Box 74)
    - Kevin Killian and Amy Adler, photo by James Gobel, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Pierre Guyotat, photo by Matt Fishbeck, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Edmund White, photo by Cheryl Meeker, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Edmund Berrigan, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Mattilda, photo by Adrian Brooks, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Job Piston, photo by William E. Jones, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian, photo by Andrew Kenower, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Valerie Estes, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Tanya Hollis, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian, George Albon, Jocelyn Saidenberg, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian in Bob Holman's glasses, photo by Bob Holman, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian in Buffalo flanked by Derek McCormack and Jason McBride, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian invested in the Red Lobster Club, October 2009, 2009 October (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and House of Radar shirts, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin rear view, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian as Ahab in The Fiery Hunt, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian on a UFO mirror by Kota Ezawa, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and his picture on a lightbox by Kota Ezawa, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Stephanie Schiff, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy, photographed by Tariq Alvi, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy's 20th anniversary cake, July 3, 2006, 2006 July 03 (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and R.H. Quaytman, photographed by Apsara DiQuinzio, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Travis Jeppesen, photographed by George Kuchar, undated (Box 66)
    - Kevin Killian and Bob Gluck, photographed by Ron Palmer, undated (Box 66)
    - Maureen, Catherine, Nancy Killian, undated (Box 66)
    - Maureen Killian, undated (Box 66)
    - Maureen Killian with Desmond or Rory, undated (Box 66)
    - Maureen Killian Dave Brooks on park, undated (Box 66)
    - Bench, Washington Square Park, undated (Box 66)
    - Raymond Killian, undated (Box 66)
    - Geraldine Kim, undated (Box 66)
    - Burt Kimmelman, undated (Box 66)
    - Basil and Martha King, undated (Box 66)
    - Laurie R. King, undated (Box 66)
    - Stephen King, photo by Loss Glazier, undated (Box 74)
    - Maxine Hong Kingston, undated (Box 66)
    - Martha Kinney, undated (Box 66)
    - Lynn Kirby, undated (Box 66)
    - Mike Kitchell, undated (Box 66)
    - Amy Klein, undated (Box 66)
    - Kleinertalstrasse, 83, Basel, undated (Box 66)
    - Andrew Klobucar, undated (Box 66)
    - Ken Knabb, undated (Box 66)
    - Savannah Knoop, the one who posed as JT Leroy, undated (Box 66)
    - John Koch, undated (Box 66)
    - Kenneth Koch, undated (Box 66)
    - Auden and Rodney Koeneke, undated (Box 66)
    - Rodney Koeneke, undated (Box 66)
    - Wayne Koestenbaum, undated (Box 66)
    - Wayne Koestenbaum and Dodie Bellamy, undated (Box 66)
    - Terence Koh, undated (Box 66)
    - Fred Kolouch, undated (Box 66)
    - Chris Komater, undated (Box 66)
    - Rem Koolhaas Seattle Library, undated (Box 66)
    - Josh Kornbluth, undated (Box 66)
    - Deirdre Kovac, undated (Box 66)
    - Harley Jane Kozak, undated (Box 66)
    - Wendy Kramer, undated (Box 66)
    - Wendy Kramer and Rafiq, undated (Box 66)
    - Chris Kraus, undated (Box 66)
    - Tim Kreiner, undated (Box 66)
    - Stuart Krimko, undated (Box 66)
    - Pavel Kruk, undated (Box 66)
    - George Kuchar, undated (Box 66)
    - Mike Kuchar, undated (Box 66)
    - Gina Kumani, undated (Box 66)
    - Aaron Kunin, undated (Box 66)
    - Green leaves at the Kunsthalle bar, Basel, undated (Box 66)
    - Katie Kurtz, undated (Box 66)
    - Steve Kurtz, Critical Art Ensemble, undated (Box 66)
    - Rachel Kushner, undated (Box 66)
    - Joel Kuszai, undated (Box 67)
    - Joanne Kyger, undated (Box 67)
    - Kylie Minogue cake for Kevin Killian's birthday, undated (Box 67)
    - Sean Manzano Labrador, undated (Box 67)
    - Bruce La Bruce, undated (Box 67)
    - Steve Lafreniere and Dodie Bellamy, undated (Box 67)
    - Lai wan, undated (Box 67)
    - George Lakoff, undated (Box 67)
    - Philip Lamantia, undated (Box 67)
    - Joshua Lamm, undated (Box 67)
    - Susan Landers, undated (Box 67)
    - John Landry, undated (Box 67)
    - Lands End, San Francisco, undated (Box 67)
    - Doug Lang, undated (Box 67)
    - Joan Larkin, undated (Box 67)
    - Robert Larkin, undated (Box 67)
    - Jeremy Larner, undated (Box 67)
    - David Larsen, undated (Box 67)
    - Dorothea Lasky, undated (Box 67)
    - Last Day of Dodie's summer writing workshop, undated (Box 67)
    - Ann Lauterbach, undated (Box 67)
    - Ann Lauterbach with Alex Katz' picture of her, undated (Box 67)
    - Andrea Lawlor, undated (Box 67)
    - Jane Lea, undated (Box 67)